gamerlots.com 2015-12-18

# Privacy Policy

**_1\. Introduction_**

BoomeranGO, Inc. is the official proprietor of GamerLots.com. This privacy statement indicates the way we collect and use the personal information you provide on our website. GamerLots.com abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

**_2\. General_**

Traditionally for the most websites, we gather information automatically and store it in log files. This information contains internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click-stream data. We use this information to analyze trends, to administer the website, to track visitors’ movements around the site and to gather information about the geographic location of our visitors as a whole. All the information you provide us with is used to make your experience on our website well-tailored according to your personal needs and preferences in terms of content, advertising and other current and future needs. You may choose not to register on our website and in this case we will not have access to your personal data. 

The way communication is performed on the Internet is between the pairs of IP-addresses. The IP address from which the connection is made will be logged by our Web servers. The IP addresses are used primarily to effectively deal with technical problems if required and prevent abuse of other site users or the system. 

GamerLots.com can collect personal information from you on a voluntary basis. This information may include personal information such as your name and e-mail address. Such information is collected in case you write an inquiry letter using our Support form which can be found on the Contact Us page of the website or in case you provide your email address in the authorization form. 

By allowing you to send e-mail to us, we are not attempting to collect any personal information about you. We will only use personal information (such as name and e-mail address) contained in your e-mail to respond to your specific inquiry or comments in the e-mail. Although we may retain your e-mail for a period of time, we will not use any personal information contained in your e-mail for any purpose other than responding to your specific inquiry or comments. When you fill in an authorization form we ask you to create a unique nickname and a password which we store in our database in an encrypted form.

**_3\. Internet Safety_**

We take all necessary security arrangements to protect against unauthorized access, unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include domestic reviews of our data base, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. We strongly recommend that Parents take time to communicate and educate their children about Internet Safety. GamerLots.com is not intended for children under the age of 13. On our website the user is not asked for age however any website visitor should comply with our Terms of Use which conspicuously state that by the fact of using this website you admit being 13 years old or older.

It is recommended that parents supervise their children’s use of the Internet services and online activities or when direct supervision is not possible turn on special parental control tools that block kid-unfriendly resources as well as prevent children from providing any of their personal information online. 

**_4\. Use of Information and Information Sharing_**

**_4.1 Cookies_**

A "cookie" is a small file that contains a line of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. However, we do not use cookies to store personal information such as your name. You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer. 

**_4.2 Third-Party Vendor Cookies_**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Any user should pay attention to the fact that the way other companies use cookies is dependent upon and regulated by their own privacy policy. Thus, Google, as a third party supplier, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Even though this type of cookies make it possible to serve targeted advertisements in your browser (based on your search interests and previous browser history, for example) they do not any “personally identifiable information” like name, physical address, phone number, social securityor bank account number. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

BoomeranGO, Inc. also makes use of such services as Google Analytics Demographics and several similar services by Google

Third parties, like Google may collect certain types of information about visits to the websites as well as your content interaction on these websites. However, no personally identifiable information will be collected.

We will only share the information we receive from you with the third-parties who perform services for us and not with anybody else. 

At the same time we would like to inform our users that we may disclose the information you provide if required to do so by law or we have good faith and belief that such disclosure is necessary to (1) defend and/or protect our rights or property, (2) in case of an emergency when it is necessary to protect someone’s life and/or safety, (3) to comply with a legal procedure or law if those are served on us.

**_5\. Other_**

GamerLots.com may offer such additional options as user reviews, chat conversations, multi-player games or other public options. You should be aware of the fact that any information posted by you through these services/options will be considered public and available to all other website users. All website users should be aware of the fact that for their own safety it would be reasonable not to use personal and personally identifiable information in a screen name or other publicly available information.

BoomeranGO, Inc. uses all efforts to protect the information safety of its users: we exercise the necessary measures to avoid the loss, misuse or alteration of the information that is under our control. However, we cannot guarantee absolute security of any information that is transmitted over the Internet and we will not be liable for any unintentional information disclosure.

In case you choose to inform a friend about our services and/or our website we will ask you for that friend’s email address in order to send them a one-time email inviting them to visit our website. We also store this information for a short period of time and for the only purpose of sending the one-time email. 

**_6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy_**

Your use of our website is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of UseWe retain the right to make changes in this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes in a conspicuous manner to this Privacy Policy.

**_7\. Contact Information_**

Please use our contact form if you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy.
